[{
    "question": "1. Is AngularJs is a Open source?",
     "options":["True","False"],
      "answer":0

    },
    {
        "question":"2. who was known as Iron man of India?",
        "options":["Govind Ballabh Pant","Jawaharlal Nehru","Subhash Chandra Bose","Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel"],
        "answer":3

    },
   
    {
        "question":"3. Which of the following is used in pencils?",
        "options":["Graphite","Silicon","Charcoal","Phosphorous"],
        "answer":0

    },
    {
        "question":"4. Which county did Ravi Shastri play for?",
        "options":["Leicestershire","Gloucestershire","Lancashire","Glamorgan"],
        "answer":3
    },
    {
        "question":"5. Which was the 1st non Test playing country to beat India in an international match?",
        "options":["Canada","Zimbabwe","Sri Lanka","East Africa"],
        "answer":2

    },
    {
        "question":"6. Which batsman started his international cricketing career at the age of 16?",
        "options":["Suresh Raina","Piyush Chawla","Rahul Dravid","Sachin Tendulkar"],
        "answer":3

    },
    {
        "question":"7.In which decade was the American Institute of Electrical Engineers (AIEE) founded?",
        "options":["1850s","1880s","1930s","1950s"],
        "answer":1

    },
    {
        "question":"8.'Dandia' is a popular dance of",
        "options":["Punjab","Gujarat","Tamil Nadu","Maharashtra"],
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "question":"9.Who is the first Indian woman to win an Asian Games gold in 400m run?",
        "options":["M.L.Valsamma","P.T.Usha","Kamaljit Sandhu","K.Malleshwari"],
        "answer":2
    },
    {
        "question":"10.What is 24x2?",
        "options":["38","28","68","48"],
        "answer":3
    }

 ]   











